Guide to the Cornell University College of Arts and Sciences records,1905-1993.
Cornell University College of Arts and Sciences records,1905-1993
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University College of Arts and Sciences records, 1905-1993.
14-2-767
Cornell University. College of Arts and Sciences.
26 cubic ft. and 9 videos
Correspondence, reports, and other records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence of Deans Robert M. Ogden, Cornelis Willem de Kiewiet, Leonard S. Cottrell, Paul M. O'Leary, and Francis E. Mineka with members of the faculty and administration; reports of department heads to the Deans; actions of the Board of Trustees; correspondence and reports dealing with faculty appointments, promotions, working conditions, departmental plans, curricula, research, budgets, the School of Education, the work of various committees of the College, the administration of the Dean's Office, and other matters.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence of Deans Robert M. Ogden, Cornelis Willem de Kiewiet, Leonard S. Cottrell, Paul M. O'Leary, and Francis E. Mineka with members of the faculty and administration; reports of department heads to the Deans; actions of the Board of Trustees; correspondence and reports dealing with faculty appointments, promotions, working conditions, departmental plans, curricula, research, budgets, the School of Education, the work of various committees of the College, the administration of the Dean's Office, and other matters.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cottrell, Leonard S.; de Kiewiet, C. W.(Cornelius William), 1902-; Mineka, Francis E.; O'Leary, Paul M.; Ogden, Robert M.; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell University. College of Arts and Sciences. Office of the Dean.; Cornell University. College of Arts and Sciences--Students.; Cornell University. College of Arts and Sciences--Faculty.; Cornell University. College of Arts and Sciences--Faculty--Salaries, pensions, etc.; Cornell University. College of Arts and Sciences--Administration.; Cornell University. College of Arts and Sciences--Curricula.; Cornell University. College of Arts and Sciences--Degrees.; Cornell University. College of Arts and Sciences--Statistics.; Cornell University. College of Arts and Sciences--Finance.; Cornell University. Board of Trustees.
Subjects:
Education--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Deans.
Form and Genre Terms:
Videotapes.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Boxes 22, 23, 24 and 26 are restricted in part; permission of the office of origin.
Registrar’s cards in boxes 15-18 are to be requested by student name.
CONTAINER LIST
- American Council of Learned Societies, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- American Council of Learned Societies, 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- American Historical Association, 1945-1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- American Historical Association. Guy Stanton Ford (Herbert Baxter Adams Prize), 1944 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- American Institute of Pacific Relations, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Applications, 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Applications, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Applications, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Area and Language Training Program, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Army ASTP Program - General, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Army Basic Programs, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Army and Navy Programs, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Army and Navy Programs, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- A.S.T.- U.S.M.A. Program (C.W. Jones), 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Association of American Colleges, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Association of Scientists of Cornell University, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- B - Miscellaneous, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- C - Miscellaneous, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Central European Affairs Institute - Proposal to establish at Cornell, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- D - Miscellaneous, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Mrs Day, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Dean's Group, 1944-1948 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- F - Miscellaneous, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Foreign Relations Council, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Foreign Students in the University, 1934-1947 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Form Letters, 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- G - Miscellaneous, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Graduate School, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Guggenheim Foundation, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- H - Miscellaneous, 1945-1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- History Applications, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- I - Miscellaneous, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Institute of Current World Affairs, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- J - Miscellaneous, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- K - Miscellaneous, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- L - Miscellaneous, 1945-1948 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- M - Miscellaneous 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Miscellaneous, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- N - Miscellaneous, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- National Education Association of the United States, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Navy Basic Program, 1943-1946 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Navy Basic Program, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- New York State Department of Education (Box 1, Folder 43)
- O - Miscellaneous, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Orientation - Freshman, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- P - Miscellaneous, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Phi Beta Kappa, 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Phi Kappa Phi, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- R - Miscellaneous, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Russian Library Cartel, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Russian Army Program, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Rockefeller Foundation - Correspondence with John Marshall, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- S - Miscellaneous, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Scholastic and Aptitude Tests, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Science Department Meetings, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Selective Service, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Social Science Research Council, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Statistics, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Students (General), 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- T - Miscellaneous, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Textbook Projects (Silver Burdette Co.), 1943 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- V - Miscellaneous, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- W - Miscellaneous, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Who's Who in America, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Women Students, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Y - Miscellaneous, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Z - Miscellaneous, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Rockefeller Grants, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Letters for the President, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Faculty Travel, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- A.C.L.S. Committee on Fellowships amd Grants (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Correspondence with Chairmen, 1945-1948 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Foundations of National Power, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Computation Laboratory, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Psychology Committee, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- English Committee, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Pre-Medical Study Committee, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Committee on Division of General Studies, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Committee to Study Establishment of a Division, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Kenneth Reed Scholarship Committee), 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Proposed Division of Social Studies, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- General Science Course, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Educational Policy Cooperative Course, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Educational Policy Service Courses, 1945-1948 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Educational Policy Committee, 1944-1949 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Educational Policy Meeting Transcripts, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Educational Policy Meeting Minutes, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Academic Records Committee, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Class Scheduling Committee, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- University Lectures Committee, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Registrar Reports, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Student Hours of Instruction (Box 2, Folder 26)
- College Announcements, 1945-1947 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Improvement, 1945-1947 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Class Attendance Before and After Holidays, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Spring Term Quotas, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Spring Term Quotas, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Fall Term Quotas, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Spring Term, Fall Term, Graduate Quotas, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Grad School Space Quotas, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- General, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Admissions, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Dean of University Faculty, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- General University Faculty, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- University and Federal Government, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Student Foreign Exchange, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Alumni Secretary, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Medical Office, 1942, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Director of Admissions, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Buildings and Grounds, 1944-1947 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Language Programs, 1945-1947 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Arts and Science Curriculum, 1945-1947 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Dean of the College, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Dean's Office, 1945-1948 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Project Work Sheets, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Organization of Dean's Office, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- College Pre-Registration, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Annual Reports, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Bulletins and Pamphlets, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Graduate Quota Committee, 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Correspondence Related to Various Companies, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Budget of the College Submitted to the President, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Budget Material, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Letters from India, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- E - Miscellaneous, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- American Council on Education, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- A - Miscellaneous, 1946-1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Prizes - The Dean's Prize, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Teaching Loads, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Chemistry, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Economics, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- English, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Geology and History, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Mathematics, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Modern Language, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Music and Physics, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Psychology, Sociology, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Speech, Drama and Zoology, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Survey of Assistantships at Cornell, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Report on Salaries of Assistants, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Study of Salary Increases and Promotions, 1941-1946 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Term Appointments, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Spring Term Appointments, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Advisory and Counseling Services, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Travel Funds for Faculty Members, 1944-1948 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Dean's List, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Music Department, 1944-1946 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Purchasing Office, Employment and Placement Services, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Fraternities, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- The Secretary, Treasurer and Vice President, 1945-1947 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- The President, Provost, 1946-1948 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Board of Trustees, Trustee Actions, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Research Projects, 1938, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Cornelius Betten, 1935-1940 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Dean of University Faculty, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Trustee Actions, 1923-1926 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Trustee Actions, 1926-1928 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Trustee Actions, 1928-1930 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Trustee Actions, 1930-1932 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Trustee Actions, 1932-1936 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Trustee Actions, 1934-1937 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Trustee Actions, 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Trustee Actions, 1939-1941 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Trustee Actions, 1941-1943 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Trustee Actions, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Social Studies - Correspondence, 1945-1948 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Division of Modern Foreign Languages, 1945-1948 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Division of Modern Foreign Languages - Corresondence, 1945-1948 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Correspondence and Literature on Reconstruction of Modern Language Work, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Scandinavian Languages Correspondence, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Committee of Division of Literature, Minutes of Meetings, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- University Resource Center in Connection with United Nations, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Astronomy, 1944-1947 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Chemistry Department, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Chemistry Department, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Chemistry Appointments, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Classics, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Economics Department, 1944-1947 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Economics Department, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Economics Department, Appointments, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- English Department, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- English Department, Appointments, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Far Eastern Studies Department, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Far Eastern Studies, Appointments, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Fine Arts Department Includes Appointments, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Geology Department, Newsletter Includes Appointments, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Geology Department Includes Appointments, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- German Department Includes Appointments, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Government Department Includes Appointments, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- History of Science For Engineering Students, 1946-1948 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Literature Department, 1946-1949 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Modern Languages Department, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Modern Languages Department, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Modern Languages, Appointments, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Music Department Includes Appointments, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Philosophy Department Includes Appointments, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Physics Department, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Physics Appointments, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Physics Appointments, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Psychology Department, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Psychology Department, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Committee on Russian Studies, 1948-1951 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Russian Studies, 1945-1948 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Russian Studies Department, 1944-1947 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Scoiology, 1946-1948 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Sociology and Anthropology, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Sociology Department, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Sociology and Anthropology Appointments, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Sociology Appointments, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Speech and Drama Department, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Speech and Drama Department, 1944-1948 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Zoology Department, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Zoology Department, 1944-1948 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Requests for Additional Space, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Needs of Departments, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Library Acquisitions Lists, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Registration for Courses, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Budget, 1924-1925 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Budget and Budget Estimates, 1925-1926 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Budget and Budget Estimates, 1926-1927 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Budget Estimates, 1927-1928 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Budget, 1927-1928 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Budget Estimates, 1928-1929 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Budget, 1928-1929 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Budget Estimates, 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Budget, 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Buget Estimates, 1929-1931 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Budget, 1930-1931 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Budget and Budget Estimates, 1931-1932 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Budget and Budget Estimates, 1932-1933 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Budget and Budget Estimates, 1933-1934 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Budget and Budget Estimates, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Budget Estimates, 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Budget Estimates, 1935-1937 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Budget and Budget Estimates, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Budget Estimates, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Budget, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Budget Estimates, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Budget Estimates, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Budget, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Budget Estimates, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Budget, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Budget Estimates, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Summer Payroll, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Budgets, 1944-1947 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Budget Final, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Budget, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Budget, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Budget Requests, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Budget Final, 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Annual Reports, 1923-1924 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Annual Reports, 1928-1929 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Annual Reports, 1929-1930 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Annual Reports, 1931-1933 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Annual Reports, 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Annual Reports, 1935-1938 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Annual Reports, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Annual Reports, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Annual Reports, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Annual Reports, 1941-1942 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Annual Reports, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Annual Reports, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Annual Reports, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Annual Reports, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Annual Reports, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Annual Reports, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Annual Reports, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Annual Reports, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Annual Reports, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Annual Reports, 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Annual Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Annual Reports, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Annual Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Annual Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Annual Reports, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Faculty (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Departmental Reports, 1922-1923 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Departmental Reports, 1923-1924 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Departmental Reports, 1924-1925 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Departmental Reports, 1925-1926 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Departmental Reports, 1926-1927 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Departmental Reports, 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Departmental Reports, 1928-1929 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Departmental Reports, 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Departmental Reports, 1930-1931 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Departmental Reports, 1931-1932 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Departmental Reports, 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Departmental Reports, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Departmental Reports, 1935-1936 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Departmental Reports, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Departmental Reports, 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Departmental Reports, 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Departmental Reports, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Departmental Reports, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Astronomy, 1927-1944 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Chemistry, 1924-1930 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Chemistry, 1930-1935 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Chemistry, 1936-1939 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Chemistry, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Chemistry, 1941-1943 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Chemistry, 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Classics, 1924-1935 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Classics, 1935-1944 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- German, 1923-1934 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- German, 1935-1944 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Government, 1923-1935 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Government, 1935-1944 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Mathematics, 1923-1935 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Mathematics, 1935-1939 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Mathematics, 1940-1943 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Mathematics, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Mathematics - Appointments, 1947-1949 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Mathematics Department, 1947-1949 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Music, 1920-1929 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Music, 1929-1935 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Music, 1936-1939 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Music, 1940-1943 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Music Department, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Philosophy, 1923-1935 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Philosophy, 1935-1939 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Philosophy, 1940-1943 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Physics, 1923-1929 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Physics, 1929-1935 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Physics, 1936-1939 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Physics, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Economics, 1923-1930 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Economics, 1930-1935 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Economics, 1936-1943 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- English, 1923-1935 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- English, 1935-1939 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- English, 1940-1942 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- English, 1942-1944 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Fine Arts, 1936-1939 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Fine Arts, 1940-1944 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Geology, 1923-1930 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Geology, 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Geology, 1935-1937 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Geology, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Geology, 1940-1944 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- History, 1924-1929 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- History, 1929-1935 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- History, 1936-1939 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- History, 1940-1944 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- History Department, Appointments, 1947-1949 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Candidates for A. B. Degree, 1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Candidates for A. B. Degree, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Candidates for A. B. Degree, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Candidates for A. B. Degree, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Candidates for A. B. Degree, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Candidates for A. B. Degree, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Graduates, 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Graduates, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Physics Department, 1941-1943 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Physics Department, 1943-1945 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Physics Department, 1944-1946 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Psychology, 1924-1928 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Psychology, 1928-1935 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Psychology, 1936-1939 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Psychology, 1940-1944 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Psychology, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Public Speaking, 1922-1935 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Public Speaking, 1936-1942 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Speech and Drama, 1942-1944 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Romance Languages, 1923-1935 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Romance Languages, 1935-1939 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Romance Languages, 1940-1944 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Scandinavian Language, 1927-1946 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Russian Language and Literature, 1939-1942 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Slavic Language and Literature, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Slavic Language and Literature, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Sociology and Anthropology, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Sociology and Anthropology, 1941-1943 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Sociology and Anthropology, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Animal Biology, 1929-1935 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Biology, 1935-1939 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Zoology, 1937-1939 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Zoology - Dean Ogden's File, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Zoology, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Zoology, 1940-1943 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Zoology, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- American Studies, 1949-1951 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- American Values, 1948-1950 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Biblical Studies, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Biblical Studies - Theodore Gaster, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Biblical Studies - Cyrus Gordon, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Biblical Studies - Netanyahu, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Biblical Studies - Chaim Raphael, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Biblical Studies - Nahum Sarna, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Biblical Studies - Morton Smith, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Biblical Studies - Wernberg-Moller, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Boguslavsky Case, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Committee on Economy, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Construction Requests, 1954-1955 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Salaries for Assistants, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Arts College Faculty Instructors, 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Library Building Committee, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Rockefeller Grant for Development of Slavic Studies, 1945-1950 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Marcus Singer, 1954-1959 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- War Potential (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Trustee Actions, 1952-1956 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Trustee Actions, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Trustee Actions, 1946-1949 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Comparative Study of Literature, 1927-1943 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Education, 1925-1934 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Education, 1934-1939 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Education, 1940-1941 (Box 12, Folder 8)